Ending
You are right
I had my assistant Rinri come over today.
Rinri was actually off today.
Yes, she was off today.
She came on short notice.
I was still sleeping when Keiji called me.
I was still in bed when Keiji called me.
I was brushing my teeth.
Like that, I am dancing now.
In that metaverse space.
Yeah.
You can't dance like that in the actual venue.
I would never dance.
There is a space, but you can't dance.
How long do you think it will be?
Realistically, two or three months.
About two months.
We did it at a very fast pace,
We really started in February,
I started in March, or was it a month?
But I think we worked on it for about two months.
At the longest point, we were in the studio for 12 hours.
Twelve hours and a half?
That's right.
That's a lot.
I would do four or six hours a day, every day,
I did it for about a month, and when it was really long, I did it for 12 hours,
Please take a look at my efforts.
That's right. I was completely alone.
Sometimes, Ayumi would come to dance next to me,
I was like, "What's that? I was like, "Why are you here? Why are you here?
Do you want to watch? I would say, "Why aren't you there?
That was the only thing I looked forward to.
Oh, really?
I don't know why everyone didn't see it.
But there was a time when I wasn't sure if I wanted to go.
That's right. Ue-chan came to visit once.
But it was at the very beginning.
She was working nearby and came because I was there,
She was like, "Please don't show me.
Even though she was coming into the studio over there,
But she said, "Please don't show it to me.
Don't show it to me.
He said, "You're the one who came in.
There was a case, wasn't there?
But Rinrin came because it was today,
The first time she came.
The first one.
I told you so, didn't I? On her blog.
I said I would be the first one in.
I said I'd let you in, so today, I'm here first.
I came.
I called Rin Rin,
Everyone else didn't see anything,
Some of them are coming tomorrow,
Some of them will come tomorrow, and some of them will come on another day because they are between jobs,
I am looking forward to seeing their reactions.
Rinri's idea is enduring.
What do you think?
How did I do that earlier?
Like this.
I did it the worst way.
Which is better?
This one,
Is it easier to see?
I don't know.
I feel like I'm drawing too much weight,
Where's the pin?
It's well-balanced.
Is it still easier to see?
It has a different meaning, doesn't it?
Yes, that's it.
This is Annie's connotation.
Did I do it this way before?
Is it okay if I do it this way too?
I don't care if we do it this way, too.
Not that way?Not that way?
It's this way.
It's done.
Was it 92.4 or 93?
I think it's 93.
93 is fine.
Forty-six.
28.
Yes, here.
OK!
It's slanted, though.
It's a little too far.
A little more?
Okay?
It's going to stick.
Oh, but it's good, right?
Oh, it's good, isn't it?
Yeah, it's done!
OK!
It's done!
Okay, we should start like this.
Phew!
Nice!
Nice, huh?
Where's the middle?
Right here?
Right there?
Right there, right there?
Okay, here we go.
A little too choppy, huh?
I'm gonna write something twice later.
I was thinking capital letters, lowercase.
Lowercase.
Lowercase?
All of them?
All of them.
Okay, let's just put them all down for a second.
Let's do another coat later.
It's a little...
It's too poofy.
That's good.
Yeah, it is.
But not too much.
No, but it's a little more...
I want to make it all black.
I'd like to get rid of these pimples.
Then paint it easier?
I'll do it.
There's a lot more water than you think.
Easy to apply.
Oh, that's good, right?
It's good.
It's okay.
I did it. I got him.
Did you fake it?
I did it.
Okay, nice!
Okay, okay, okay.
Follow it, follow it, follow it.
Work hard to clean this up.
This is where I was bad.
Clean it up.
Can I make it thick again?
OK!
Okay, okay, okay.
Hey, I feel sick.
I don't know what you're wearing, kitty.
I can't stay round.
Oh! Oh, no, no, no!
Oh, no, no, no, no, no!
It's good, isn't it?
It's done!
Please write your favorite message here!
First issue
Please write anything you want.
Anything you want.
Anything you like.
Anything you likeThe ones you like.
Or a message.
Anything.
Really, anything.
Wait, super thin.
But is it okay if it's small?
Because we're going to have a lot of people coming, right?
Yeah, I guess so.
That's great.
It's great!
It's great.
OK.
Contents
I'm pretty much set, Rin Rin Rin.
Thank you very much.
The best.
It's good.
Look at that.
Wow.
This...
This "ryu" character
It's here.
This one!
I wrote it in one shot, and it's my favorite character, so much so that I definitely want to have it.
I personally like this one the best out of all the ones I've written, so if no one buys this one, I'll take it home.
If no one buys it, I'll take it home with me, so if you want it, by all means!
If there is someone named Ryu, you might want to buy it.
I'm sure there are guys named Ryu.
Ryu, Ryu, please!
I think it's really cool!
Maybe it won't be available when it's released.
I wonder if there will be a lottery for those who want it.
I think it's on the website, but I don't know how it works.
I'm sure you'll be able to apply for it and get it by lottery.
I really recommend it.
I'll definitely do it again when it changes.
I'll definitely do it again when they change it.
I'd like to be in the second half of the show more than the first half, but...
I've been writing for a month or two, and this is the last one I wrote, so my brush strokes are really different.
I can write more and more smoothly, so I feel that the ones I wrote in the last half of the year are better, in my opinion.
I mean, I can't help but think that some of them were rewritten.
I hope you enjoy the first half and the second half of the book.
I hope you enjoy the first half.
It's 155. 154 points.
It's 7.
I'll give you a 155.
I'll be dizzy if I get two 153s.
Yes, return it.
Give it back.
There is no 155.
It is 155. I'll be dizzy.
It goes like this.
It will be like this.
Yes, bye-bye.